Guide to the Rice University Athletic Director Records (Bobby May), 1987-2005 UA 185
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Athletic Director Records (Bobby May)
1987-2005
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
May, Bobby
UA 185
44 Linear Feet (88 boxes)
This collection contains former Athletic Director Bobby May's papers, including correspondence, paperwork, and records, from the years 1987 to 2005. It also contains information from his secretary, Barbara Tolar, and information pertaining to the NCAA, the WAC, Title IX, Endowments, Marketing, the Wingenroth Lawsuit, and Reckling Park.
Biographical Sketch
John Robert "Bobby" May graduated from Rice University as a student athlete in 1965. He was the Athletic Director for Rice University from 1988 to 2006. During that period the Athletics Department brought home 26 conference championships, including the 2003 NCAA baseball championship. In 2002 Rice received the USA Today/NCAA Academic Achievement Award for maintaining the top student-athlete graduation rate in the nation. Prior to serving as the Athletic Director, May worked as an assistant coach, then head coach for the Men's Track team for 12 years. May retired in 2006.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes the files of former Athletic Director Bobby May. It includes paperwork, correspondence, and records pertaining to Rice University's Athletic Department between the years 1987 and 2005. The collection is divided into 9 series: Chronological, NCAA, WAC, Title IX, Barbara Tolar, Endowments, Marketing, the Wingenroth Lawsuit, and Reckling Park.
Access Restrictions
Materials in Series VI: Endowments and Series VIII: Wingenroth lawsuit are restricted. Permission to view these materials must be obtained in writing from the Office of the Rice University Athletic Director. Other materials are open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
Bobby May Athletics Records (53 cu. ft) were received October 23, 2007.
Related Materials
May, Bobby (Woodson Research Center Information File); Athletic Department (Woodson Research Center Information File)
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Athletics; Sports
Document Types
letters (correspondence)
Places
Rice University
- Series I: Chronological, 1937-2005; 154136
  - Elva Kalb Dumas:, 1937-1938; 154137 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Scheduling Policy:, 1987-1990; 154138 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Budget Recap with Expense Reductions:, 1989-1990; 154139 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Training Table Expenses:, 1989-1992; 154140 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Automobiles:, 1990-2001; 154141 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Scheduling Policy:, 1991-2000; 154142 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tuitions:, 1993-1995; 154143 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Athletics Admissions:, 1994-1997; 154144 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budget Meeting with President Gillis:, 1994; 154145 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence:, 1994-1995; 154146 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [John L.] Cox Fitness Center:, 1994-1995; 154147 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marketing:, 1994-1995; 154148 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Athlete Donor Lists:, 1995; 154149 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Licensing:, 1995-2000; 154150 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Football Alliance Agreement:, 1995; 154151 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Football Alliance Agreement:, 1995; 155518 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Touchdown Publications/Football Programs:, 1995-1997; 154152 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Administration Staff Meetings:, 1996-1998; 154153 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Endowment:, 1996-1999; 154154 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Steering Committee:, 1996-2000; 154155 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Steering Committee:, 1996-2000; 155519 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Steering Committee Prospects:, 1996-1997; 154156 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Baseball Projects:, 1996-1997; 154157 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Baseball Projects:, 1996-1997; 154159 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board Tickets and Amenities:, 1996-1997; 154158 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Budget FY, 1996-1997; 154160 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coca-Cola Company Sponsorship Agreement:, 1996; 154161 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - College Football Player Survey:, 1996; 154162 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Computer Systems Acquisition:, 1996; 154163 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence:, 1996; 154164 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence:, 1996; 155520 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - [John L.] Cox Fitness Center:, 1996-1998; 154165 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Football Bowl Alliance:, 1996-1997; 154166 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Football Bowl Alliance:, 1996-1997; 155521 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Griswald, Julie:, 1996-1997; 154167 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Griswald, Julie:, 1996-1997; 155522 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Major Gifts Initiative for Department of Athletics:, 1996; 154168 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Miller Brewing Company Agreement:, 1996; 154169 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Owl Club:, 1996-2002; 154170 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - President's Dinner:, 1996; 154171 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Prospects:, 1996-2001; 154172 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "R" Association Income Tax Returns:, 1996-1997; 154173 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Scholarships:, 1996-1999; 154174 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Tuitions:, 1996-1999; 154175 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Golf Classic:, 1996; 154176 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Aquatic Facility Committee:, 1997; 154177 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Aquatic Facility Planning:, 1997; 154178 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Associative Athletic Director:, 1997-1998; 154179 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Athletics Financial Presentations:, 1997-2002; 154180 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Injury Claims:, 1997-1998; 154181 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Budget FY, 1997; 154182 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Budget FY, 1997; 155523 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Coaches' Contracts:, 1997-2000; 154183 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - College World Series:, 1997; 154184 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Collegiate Licensing:, 1997-1998; 154185 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Concession Services Agreement:, 1997; 154186 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence:, 1997; 154187 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence:, 1997; 155524 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence:, 1997; 154188 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Dean Allcorn:, 1997-1998; 154189 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Gift Report:, 1997-1998; 154190 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Diamond Club:, 1997-1998; 154191 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Division 1A Athletic Directors' Association:, 1997-1998; 154192 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Division 1A Athletic Directors' Association:, 1997-1998; 155525 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gifts and Pledges:, 1997-1998; 154193 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Gift Processing:, 1997-1998; 154194 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Gift Processing:, 1997-1998; 155526 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [Gene] Hackerman Scholarship:, 1997-1999; 154195 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Humanitarian Bowl:, 1997-1998; 154196 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Injury Claims:, 1997; 154197 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Jumbotron Agreement:, 1997-1998; 154198 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - KKHT and KTRK Radio Agreements:, 1997-2000; 154199 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Luncheon Presentations:, 1997-1999; 154200 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Marketing:, 1997-1998; 154201 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Medical Updates (Athletes):, 1997-1998; 154202 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NACDA (National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics):, 1997-1998; 154203 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - NACDA Executive Committee:, 1997-1998; 154204 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Owl Club Accounting:, 1997-1998; 154205 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Owl Club Personalized Parking:, 1997-1998; 154206 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Practice Gym:, 1997-1998; 154207 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - President Gillis Staff Meetings:, 1997-1999; 154208 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prop 62:, 1997; 154209 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - RUAC (Rice University Athletics Committee):, 1997-1998; 154210 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - San Juan Basketball Tournament: Nov 26-Dec 1, 1997; 154211 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Sellout Operation:, 1997; 154212 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Doug:, 1997-1998; 154213 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Summer Strength and Conditioning (Football):, 1997-1999; 154214 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Team Concept Mini Fund Drive:, 1997-1998; 154215 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Transition Notes:, 1997; 154216 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Tuitions:, 1997-1998; 154217 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Women's Golf Classic:, 1997-1998; 154218 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Academic Coordinator:, 1998-1999; 154219 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Injury Claims:, 1998-1999; 154220 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Licensing:, 1998-1999; 154221 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Steering Committee:, 1998; 154222 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - [New] Baseball Facility:, 1998-1999; 154223 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - [New] Baseball Facility:, 1998-1999; 155527 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Budget FY, 1998; 154224 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Budget FY, 1998; 155528 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Budget:, 1998-1999; 154225 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Budget:, 1998-1999; 155529 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Budget:, 1998-1999; 155530 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Budget:, 1998-1999; 155531 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Capital Budget:, 1998-1999; 154226 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Champs/Life Skills Program:, 1998; 154227 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence:, 1998; 154228 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence:, 1998; 155532 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence:, 1998; 155533 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - [McNair] Golf Program Proposals/Golf Coach Search:, 1998; 154229 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Medical Updates:, 1998-1999; 154230 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NACDA (National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics):, 1998-1999; 154231 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NACDA Executive Committee:, 1998-1999; 154232 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Owl Club Fund Drive Manual:, 1998; 154233 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ring of Honor:, 1998; 154234 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - RUAC (Rice University Athletics Committee):, 1998-1999; 154235 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Sellout SMU:, 1998; 154236 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meetings:, 1998-1999; 154237 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Sterling Bank Business Development Board:, 1998-1999; 154238 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - [George] Strait Concerts:, 1998-1999; 154239 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tuitions:, 1998-2003; 154240 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - University Website and Cybercast Agreement:, 1998; 154241 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Adidas Legal:, 1999; 154242 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Athletics Gifts:, 1999; 154243 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Budget:, 1999-2000; 154244 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Budget:, 1999-2000; 154245 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Leadership Committee:, 1999; 154246 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence:, 1999; 154247 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence:, 1999; 155534 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence:, 1999; 155535 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Division I-A Athletic Directors' Association:, 1999-2000; 154248 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Executive Golf Tournament:, 1999; 154249 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fox Television Agreement:, 1999-2000; 154250 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Graduation Rates:, 1999-2001; 154251 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Graduation Rates Reports:, 1999-2003; 154252 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Julie Griswold:, 1999-2000; 154253 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Houston Bowl (Proposed):, 1999; 154254 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Media releases (WAC, Rice):, 1999-2000; 154255 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Medical Updates:, 1999-2000; 154257 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA) Executive Committee:, 1999-2000; 154258 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "No Upper Limit":, 1999; 154259 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Operation Sellout - Rice v. Navy: September 25, 1999; 154260 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Owl Club Strategic Plan:, 1999; 154261 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Parking Advisory Committee:, 1999-2000; 154262 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - President's Staff Meetings:, 1999-2000; 154263 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "R" Association:, 1999-2003; 154264 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "R" Association Financial Statement:, 1999-2003; 154265 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "R" Association Meeting Minutes:, 1999-2003; 154266 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rice University Athletics Committee (RUAC):, 1999-2000; 154267 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships:, 1999-2000; 154268 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Women's National Invitational Tournament:, 1999; 154269 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Athletics Gifts:, 2000; 154270 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Bayou Bucket Luncheon:, 2000; 154274 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Budget FY, 2000; 154275 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Budget FY, 2000; 154276 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Campus Store, ad hoc Committee on:, 2000; 154277 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chevy Blazer Raffle:, 2000; 154278 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence:, 2000; 154279 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence:, 2000; 155536 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence:, 2000; 155537 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence:, 2000; 154280 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence:, 2000; 155538 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Enrollment Retreat:, 2000; 154281 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Equity in Athletics Disclosure Act:, 2000; 154282 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Executive Cup Golf Tournament:, 2000; 154283 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Former Athletes Roster:, 2000; 154284 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Fresno Football Player Incident:, 2000; 154285 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising Audit:, 2000; 154286 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - GAO (US General Accounting Office) Sports Termination:, 2000; 154287 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Golf Coach Search:, 2000; 154288 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - GTE Academic All-American Hall of Fame:, 2000; 154289 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Internet Sports Gambling:, 2000; 154290 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - [Recommendations and Guidelines for] Medical Coverage for Intercollegiate Athletics:, 2000; 154321 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National Association for Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA):, 2000-2001; 154322 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - NACDA Publicity:, 2000-2001; 154323 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - New Projects Construction Timeline:, 2000; 154324 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Operation Sellout:, 2000; 154325 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - OSI Marketing Proposal:, 2000; 154326 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Preseason Women's National Invitation Tournament:, 2000; 154327 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Probations and Suspensions:, 2000-2001; 154328 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Rice: The Next Century Campaign Updates:, 2000-2002; 154329 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - River Oaks Imaging and Diagnostic Contract:, 2000; 154330 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Rice University Athletics Committee (RUAC):, 2000-2002; 154331 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - RUAC Budget:, 2000-2001; 154465 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - RUAC Meetings:, 2000-2001; 154466 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - RUAC Sports Camps:, 2000-2002; 154467 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Student-Athlete Employment:, 2000; 154468 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Track/Soccer Stadium Plan:, 2000-2001; 154469 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Training Room Expansion:, 2000; 154470 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Video Display Equipment Agreement:, 2000; 154471 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Department Laptops: FY, 2001; 154472 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Athletics Gifts:, 2001-2002; 154473 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - [Final] Budget:, 2001-2002; 154474 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Budget Savings Plan: FY, 2001; 154475 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - "Buffer Zone" Rice Stadium:, 2001; 154476 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence:, 2001; 154477 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence:, 2001; 155539 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence:, 2001; 155540 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence:, 2001; 155541 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Enron Collegiate Classic:, 2001; 154478 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - ESPN Television Agreement:, 2001-2004; 154479 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - FANCARD Agreement: FY, 2001-2005; 154480 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aid Deregulation:, 2001; 154481 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - First Aid Training:, 2001-2002; 154482 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Flood Damage to Track and Tennis Courts:, 2001; 154483 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Football Scheduling:, 2001; 154484 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Football Scheduling:, 2001; 155542 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Fox Sports Agreement:, 2001-2002; 154485 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Gifts to Athletic Department:, 2001-2002; 154486 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Humanitarian Bowl:, 2001; 154487 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Media Releases:, 2001-2002; 154488 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Media Releases:, 2001-2002; 154489 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Media Releases:, 2001-2002; 155543 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Media Releases:, 2001-2002; 155544 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Media Releases:, 2001-2002; 155545 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Medical Updates:, 2001-2002; 154490 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA):, 2001-2002; 154491 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - NACDA Mid-Winter Meeting:, 2001; 154492 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - NACDA-Sears Director's Cup Standings:, 2001-2002; 154493 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - National Invitational Tournament:, 2001; 154494 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NFFC Hall of Fame (Joe Watson):, 2001; 154495 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Pinnacle Video Editing System:, 2001; 154496 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Salary Surveys:, 2001-2002; 154497 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Scholar Awards:, 2001-2003; 154498 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Game Rescheduling September 11, 2001; 154499 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Student-Athlete Aid:, 2001; 154500 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Women's National Invitation Tournament (WNIT):, 2001-2002; 154501 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Endowment:, 2002-2003; 154502 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Endowment:, 2002-2003; 155546 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Baseball National Championship:, 2002-2003; 154503 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Baseball National Championship Rings:, 2002-2003; 154504 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Budget FY, 2002; 154505 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Budget FY, 2002; 155547 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 154506 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 155548 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 155549 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 155550 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 154507 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Budget:, 2002-2003; 155551 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Budget Preparatory Information: FY, 2002; 154508 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Budget Preparatory Information: FY, 2002; 155556 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Budget Savings Plan: FY, 2002; 154509 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Budget Status:, 2002; 154510 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - College World Series:, 2002; 154511 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence:, 2002; 154512 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence:, 2002-2003; 154513 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence:, 2002-2003; 155557 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Reports:, 2002; 154514 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Financial Comparisons/Expenditures:, 2002-2003; 154515 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Financial Comparisons/Expenditures:, 2002-2003; 154516 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Health Behavior Report:, 2002; 154517 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Honor Council:, 2002-2003; 154518 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Licensing- Florida Atlantic:, 2002; 154519 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Medical Updates:, 2002-2003; 154520 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - National Association for Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA):, 2002-2003; 154521 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - NACDA Mid-Winter Meeting:, 2002; 154522 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - On-Line Travel: FY, 2002; 154523 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Owl Club Board Meeting: November 5, 2002; 154524 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - President's Staff Meeting:, 2002; 154525 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Probations/Suspensions:, 2002-2003; 154526 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Reliant Park License Agreement - Rice v. LA Tech: October 5, 2002; 154527 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Rice Sailing Program:, 2002-2003; 154726 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - "Rice: The Next Century" Status Reports:, 2002-2003; 154727 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Salary Survey:, 2002-2003; 154728 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Sports Hero Award:, 2002; 154729 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Stadium Evacuation Plan:, 2002; 154730 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Tennis Project:, 2002; 154731 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ticket Sales and Promotion Service Agreement - Operation Sellout:, 2002; 154732 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Touchdowner of Year Award:, 2002; 154733 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Associate Athletic Director - Development:, 2003; 154734 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Astros College Classic:, 2003; 154735 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Budget:, 2003-2004; 154736 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Budget:, 2003-2004; 155558 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Budget Status:, 2003-2004; 154737 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Budget Status:, 2003-2004; 154738 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Insurance:, 2003-2004; 154739 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Baseball Painting Project:, 2003-2004; 154740 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Baseball White House: November 17, 2003; 154741 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Basketball All-American Recognition:, 2003-2004; 154742 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Bayou Bucket Luncheon:, 2003; 154743 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Budget: FY, 2003; 154744 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Budget: FY, 2003; 155559 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Budget: FY, 2003; 155560 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Budget: FY, 2003; 154745 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Budget:, 2003-2005; 154746 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Budget:, 2003-2005; 155561 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Budget Status:, 2003-2005; 154747 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Cell Phones:, 2003-2005; 154748 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Collegiate Licensing Reports:, 2003-2005; 154749 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Conference Realignment:, 2003; 154750 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence:, 2003-2004; 154751 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence:, 2003-2004; 155562 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - DMN Sports Marketing, Inc. Services Agreement:, 2003; 154752 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Fiesta Bowl:, 2003; 154753 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Financial Comparisons/Expenditures:, 2003; 154754 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Football Enhancement Meeting:, 2003-2004; 154755 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Graduation Rates:, 2003; 154756 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - HIPPA:, 2003-2004; 154757 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Jerry:, 2003-2004; 154758 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Contracts:, 2003-2004; 154759 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Media Releases:, 2003-2004; 154760 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Media Releases:, 2003-2004; 155563 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Media Releases:, 2003-2004; 155564 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Medical Updates:, 2003-2004; 154761 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Moniaci, Steve:, 2003-2004; 154762 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - National Association for Collegiate Directors of Athletics (NACDA):, 2003-2005; 154763 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Old Staff Meetings:, 2003-2005; 154764 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Owl Club Board Meeting: November 19, 2003; 154765 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Pede, Mike:, 2003-2004; 154766 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Pede, Mike:, 2003-2004; 155565 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Pratapas, Mike:, 2003-2004; 154767 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Pratapas, Mike:, 2003-2004; 155566 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - "R" Association:, 2003-2005; 154768 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - "R" Association Income Statements:, 2003-2004; 154769 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Receivables Reports:, 2003-2005; 154770 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Rice University Athletic Committee (RUAC):, 2003-2005; 154771 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Super Bowl XXXVIII Host Committee:, 2003; 154772 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Swimming Incident - Rice v. UH:, 2003; 154773 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - U.S. News and World Report Survey:, 2003; 154774 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Whalen, Stephen:, 2003; 154775 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 154776 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155567 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 154777 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155568 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155569 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155570 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 154778 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155571 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Development:, 2004-2005; 155572 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Baseball Players Alumni Association:, 2004; 154779 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Bayou Bucket:, 2004; 154780 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - [New] BCS Plan:, 2004; 154781 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Bracket Buster Contract:, 2004-2005; 154782 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - [George] Bush Sports Hero Award:, 2004-2005; 154783 (Box 43, Folder 8)